http://www.salem.edu/privacy-policy

ConnectInstagramFacebookPinterestTwitterFlickr
Close AlertSalem READY, Salem STRONGVisit our Salem READY, Salem STRONG section for the latest information on Fall 2020 and COVID-19.
*
Contains all of these wordsContains any of these wordsContains none of these words
0
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Menu
Salem Ready, Salem StrongCampus Updates and NewsNow is Our Time
Video Message: Fall 2020
Letter to Salem College - Fall 2020 Update
July 16, 2020 Message from Interim President Susan Henking regarding Fall
Q&A from Virtual Student Info Session
Academic Calendar
COVID-19 Notice of Actions Taken to Reduce the Risk of Transmission
Virtual COVID-19 Training
Orientation
Health and Safety Standards, Protocols, and ResourcesScreening
Student Life and Activities
The Lucy Rose Center for Global Leadership & Career Innovation
Campus Events
Athletics
Travel
Employee Information
Guests and Visitors to CampusSign Guest and Visitor Safety Acknowledgement (Online)
Download & Sign Guest and Visitor Safety Acknowledgement (PDF)
English and Creative WritingAcademics
Welcome!
The Chaplain's Office
What's a Moravian?
Who Is Your Campus Minister?
Places to Stay
Traveling from Outside of the Area?
Orientation InformationDegree-Seeking Welcome Letter
Certificate-Seeking. Special Admit, and StepOuts Returning Welcome Letter
Refer a Student
Network 1772!
Physical Plant
Center for Global Leadership & Career InnovationInternship GuidelinesInternship Contract
Employer Services
iLEAD - Immersion into Leadership Experience and DiversityiLEAD Brochure
iLEAD Registration Form
Workshop Reflection Form
Student Affairs
Job Search
Clubs & OrganizationsClubs & OrganizationsLeadership & Service
Academic
Activism
Arts
Multicultural
More ...
Student Activities
CommunityCommunity Music SchoolWelcome!
CWW - News
Center for Women in Entrepreneurship and BusinessSalem College Women's Conference
Healthcare.gov
International Student ServicesApplication Packets for OPT and CPT
Order a Brick
CommencementCommencement Eligibility, Diplomas, and Honors Information
Teacher EducationUndergraduate ProgramsFleer Students (Men and Women over 23)
Residency Licensure
Master of Arts in Teaching (MAT)
Master of Education (MEd)
Online Master of Education in Educational Leadership (MEd)
Emergency Contact Information
Last updated: June 05, 2019The Salem Academy and College (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates salem.edu, salemacademy.com and various subdomains under each domain (“Sites”). This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of these Sites.We use your Personal Information only for providing and improving these Sites. By using the Sites, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.Information Collection And UseWhile using our Sites, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to your name, email address, or other information needed to apply for college admissions (“Personal Information”).Log DataLike many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Sites (“Log Data”).This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Sites that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.In addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze this data.CommunicationsWe may use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that you may opt out of at any time.CookiesCookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer’s hard drive.Like many sites, we use “cookies” to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Sites.SecurityThe security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.Changes To This Privacy PolicyThis Privacy Policy is effective as of January 01, 2019 and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page.We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email address you have provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on our website.
Upcoming Events
Mid-Term Break
Oct 15
12:35pm
Classes suspended
Election Day
Nov 03
12:55pm
Classes suspended.
Last day of Face-to-Face classes
Nov 24
1:05pm
Salem News
September 25, 2020
Salem College Receives Truth Initiative Grant and Pledges to Go Tobacco and Vape Free
Salem College was one of 14 colleges and universities to be awarded a grant from Truth Initiative®  to adopt a 100 percent tobacco/vape-free campus policy.
Presidential Search
Salem College
Salem College601 S. Church StreetWinston-Salem, NC 27101(336) 721-2600
2020, all rights reserved.
